Jack Benny papers, 1930-1974
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Audiovisual Materials.
  - Jack Benny Radio Broadcasts., (14 tapes)
    - The Jello Program.., (5 tapes) (Box 60, Volume VII.)
      - 14. --New Year's routine; Baldwin but-in, finishing with whispering bit; Mary recites her New Year's poem; Kenny brings Lena up to the program; Buck Benny, finishing with Dr. Schmettena.., January 3, 1937.
      - 15. --Beginning of Fred Allen feud; Buckingham Benny, window dresser from Pomona; Buck Benny.., January 10, 1937.
      - 18. --Jack getting over his cold; race track bit; Mary reads a letter from her mother; Lucy Belle visits the studio, boy next door; dream bit, with Lind Hayes doing a Fred Allen; Jack wins radio editors' poll.., January 31, 1937.
      - 19. --Jack announces his intention to play The bee tonight; phone call to Lucy Belle; Andy Devine and Lena come over to hear Jack play, also Phil's mother and Lucy Belle; violin disappears!., February 7, 1937.
      - 20. --Jack's birthday, gifts; Mary recites birthday poem; puts ad in paper asking for return of violin; Andy comes over with birthday present; guest star, Ben Bernie; he disappears!., February 14, 1937.
      - 21. --Brewster's millions, Jack reads reviews; Mary goes highbrow; announces English drawing room drama but phone call from sponsor switches to Buck Benny; Mary leaves for New York for a rest.., February 21, 1937.
      - 22. --Jack reads letter from Mary; Lena visits Kenny again; Santa Anita handicap routine; Patsy Flick appears as detective, finding Jack's violin; Jack plays The bee which segues into Plenty of money; Jack talks to Mary on the phone; makes reservation to leave for New York.., February 28, 1937.
      - 23. --First broadcast from New York, from Waldorf-Astoria; Jack meets Abe Lyman, Abe gets tough; Schlepperman pays Jack a visit; Jack cross examines little 10 year old boy who played violin on Allen's program.., March 7, 1937.
      - 24. --Broadcast from Hotel Pierre; Mary reads wire from Kenny; Abe Lyman gets tough; income tax bit; Schlepperman volunteers to sing; Mary sings You do the darndest things, baby; Fred Allen pays Jack a visit, finishing up as friends, reminiscing about their old days together in vaudeville.., March 14, 1937.
      - 25. --Third and last broadcast from New York; Jack toots his horn; worn out from night clubs and the mad pace; Mayor Mancel Talcott Waukegan pays Jack a visit; department store sketch, Jack plays the part of his father.., March 21, 1936.
      - 26. --Scene in Chicago depot boarding train; routine on train, bit with colored porter, Albuquerque; Mary recites her Easter poem; routine with Indians at Albuquerque; Phil and Andy greet gang at studio.., March 28, 1937.
      - 27. --Spring routine; Jack starts fight with Phil - switches mood; Mary gets phone call from her mother; Andy and Jack - farm routine; annoucement of popular sketch to be repeated at later date.., April 4, 1937.
      - 28. --Jack's new suit routine; Mary reads letter from her mother (April Fool's day); guest star, Gracie Allen; Buck Benny with Gracie.., April 11, 1937.
      - 29. --Jack Benny (guest star) routine; Phil Harrises opening at the Cocoanut Grove; Andy Devine; English drawing room drama, Lady Millicent's husbands.., April 18, 1937.
      - 30. --Jack butts in during Phil's opening number - I demand an apology; guest stars, Block and Sully; Jack sends everyone home - visits Andy Devine's house in the country.., April 25, 1937.
      - 31. --Fifth anniversary program; Mary reads anniversary poem; Andy comes over to congratulate Jack; reporter bit finishing up with picture of cast; Buck Benny - party - song, Let's call the whole thing off.., May 2, 1937.; (5 tapes) (Box 61)
      - 32. --Mother's day routine; Jack starts fight with Phil; Kentucky Derby; Mary reads wire from her mother requesting schoolroom play; sketch; Jack announces results of popular play contest, trailer of Ah, wilderness.., May 9, 1937.
      - 33. --Vacation plans; announcement of sketch, Ah, wilderness.., May 16, 1937.
      - 34. --Jack did not broadcast because of illness.., May 23, 1937.
      - 35. --Sick-in-bed routine; Dr. Baldy - pills; Mary gets phone call from her mother; sketch, Murder at midnight.., May 30, 1937.
      - 36. --Jack reports that his watch is missing; colored fellow comes up to return it and claim rewards; sketch, Murder at midnight - interrupted by appearance of man from finance company.., June 6, 1937.
      - 37. --Jack boasts of his physical condition - exercise routine; Mary gets phone call from her producer at Paramount; Andy visits the program - sandwiches for the girls; Jack calls up his Artists producer re: Artists and models; scene on the Paramount lot; Mary shoots a scene.., June 13, 1937.
      - 38. --Father's day routine; Jack and nearsighted makeup man - also colored valet; synopsis of Artists and models; Jack plays his scene from inside a barrel - Hey!; In tag, guest star, Charlie Winninger.., June 20, 1937.
      - 39. --Jack complains about overwork; announces his trip to Europe; Pan-American Exposition, Dallas; sentimental bit; Mary sings, Love bug will bite you; guest star, Johnny Green; piano and violin duet, Body and soul; Farewell for season.., June 27, 1937.
    - Miscellaneous tapes.., 16 items. (Box 63)
  - Other Appearances., 1955-1964.
    - Jack Benny Recording for Tahoe-Harrah's Club, 1/4" audio tapes., August 1960.; 3.0 reels (Box 62)
    - Jack Benny Introduction Tahoe, 1/4" audio tapes., August 1964.; 3.0 reels (Box 62)
    - Isaac Stern discusses Jascha Benny, 1/4" audio tape., 1.0 reel (Box 62)
    - Conversation with Jack Benny, Liz Dribben Dub, 1/4" audio tape., 1.0 reel (Box 62)
    - Pat Boone Show #19, Jack Benny segment, 16mm color composite print., 1.0 reel (Box 62)
  - Home movies and family footage.
    - Jack Benny - Joan ("Joanie") Benny - June 6-45, 16mm film., July 1937.; 1.0 reel (Box 62)
    - Jack Benny June 6-45 Misc., 16mm film., 1.0 reel (Box 62)
    - Joan Benny Wedding Newsreel Clip, 16mm film., 1.0 reel (Box 62)
- Photographs.
  - ., n.d., 1937-1941. (Box 64)
  - ., 1942-1944. (Box 65)
  - ., 1945A. (Box 66)
  - ., 1945B. (Box 67)
  - ., 1946. (Box 68)
  - ., 1947A. (Box 69)
  - ., 1947B. (Box 70)
  - ., 1948. (Box 71)
  - ., 1949. (Box 72)
  - ., 1950A. (Box 73)
  - ., 1950B. (Box 74)
  - ., 1951. (Box 75)
  - ., 1952-1953. (Box 76)
  - ., 1954. (Box 77)
  - ., 1955. (Box 78)
  - ., 1956. (Box 79)
  - Quick. vol. 2 no. 13 (). Jack Benny: being funny is serious, pp. 48-51.., March 27, 1950. (Box 79)
  - Badge. City of Beverly Hills. Honorary Dog Catcher. On the back is inscribed: Presented to Jack Benny by the Beverly Hills Chamber of Commerce in appreciation of Civil Service,., January 20, 1941.
    *Package 1: Record album. 12.
    Jack Benny speaks for the radio code. National Association of Broadcasters, 1966.
  - Biographical data, stories & articles.. (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Requests for personal appearances,., 1955-1956. (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - San Francisco personal appearance--Curran Theater,., April 21, 1953. (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Personal appearance tour,., Summer 1954. (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Requests for personal appearances,., 1949-1950. (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Personal appearance tour, ,., May 16, 1949 -June 5, 1950. (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Denver--Benny appearance re National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis,., 1948. (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Hedda Hopper radio program,., 1948. (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Friars dinner,, Waldorf, New York, 20th anniversary special broadcast., November 9. (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Korean tour,., July 1950-1951. (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Photographs--Jack Benny at office,., 1962. (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Photographs--portraits of Jack Benny and caricatures.. (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Photographs--Austin concert,., February 22, 1966. (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Photographs--Awards, miscellaneous,., 1958. (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Photographs--George Burns & Jack Benny,., 1950. (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Photographs--Fred Allen & Jack Benny,., 1939. (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Photographs--command performance, Queen Elizabeth,., 1965. (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Photographs--Jack Benny concerts,., 1962. (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Photographs--Emmy awards, Jack Benny & writers,., 1960. (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Photographs--4 wives & Jack Benny [Mrs. Phil Silvers, Mrs. Milton Berle, Mrs. Kirk Douglas, Mrs. Groucho Marx, ].., 1964. (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Photographs--Freddy De Cordova & Jack Benny,., 1961. (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Photographs--Jack Benny dressed as Gracie [Allen],., 1959. (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Photographs--grandchildren,., 1961. (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Photographs--Greek Theatre,., 1959. (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Photographs--Heart Fund dinner, San Francisco,., October 26, 1958. (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Photographs--Harrah's Club,., August 1960. (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - Photographs--Miscellaneous,., 1963. (Box 81, Folder 17)
  - Photographs--Jack Benny with Truman,., 1949. (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - Photographs--March of Dimes Humanitarian Award,., February 1960. (Box 81, Folder 19)
  - Photographs--Joanie & Jack Benny--I've got a secret,., 1963. (Box 81, Folder 20)
  - Photographs--Jane Morgan & Jack Benny at Harrah's Club, Lake Tahoe,., 1962. (Box 81, Folder 21)
  - Photographs--Wayne Newton & Newton Brothers,., 1966. (Box 81, Folder 22)
  - Photographs--Old Ladies Band, Flamingo,., 1958. (Box 81, Folder 23)
  - Photographs--Roberta Peters & Jack Benny,., 1962. (Box 81, Folder 24)
  - Photographs--Promotion moving to Tuesday night,., 1962. (Box 81, Folder 25)
  - Photographs--Rochester--Jack Benny,., 1961. (Box 81, Folder 26)
  - Photographs--Benny Rubin & Jack Benny,., 1961. (Box 81, Folder 27)
  - Photographs--Phil Silvers & Jack Benny,., 1961. (Box 81, Folder 28)
  - Photographs--Jack Benny, George Burns, Phil Silvers,., 1958. (Box 81, Folder 29)
  - Photographs--Isaac Stern & Jack Benny,., 1955. (Box 81, Folder 30)
  - Photographs--TV shows,., 1957. (Box 81, Folder 31)
  - Photographs--Waukegan School,., 1961. (Box 81, Folder 32)
  - Photographs--Don Wilson & Jack Benny,., 1961. (Box 81, Folder 33)
  - Photographs--Jack Benny & writers,., 1962. (Box 81, Folder 34)
  - Photographs--Violin,., 1953--1966. (Box 81, Folder 35)
  - Authorizations & consents,., 1940-1950. (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Bills of sale,., 1935 & 1943. (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Cattle breeding operation.. (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous.. (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Lot 16, Block 17, Track 6193, Los Angeles.. (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Stalk Eventone Corporation,., 1951. (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Gutterman vs. CBS,., 1951-1952. (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Lemert Broadcasting Company,., 1952-1953. (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Tom Noonan, purchase of material,., 1953. (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Reviews--Jack Benny, miscellaneous papers,., 1950-1953. (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Receipt, U.S. Customs,, jewelry from Japan.., 1951. (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - London Palladium contract,., 1950. (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Warehouse receipt & contract, Bekins,., 1945-1951. (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Mary Livingstone Amusement Enterprises,., 1948-1955. (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Inventory 1002 N. Roxbury, Beverly Hills.. (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - American Tobacco Company correspondence,., 1947-1951. (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - MCA--CBS agreements and consents.. (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - advertisements.., 1951-1951. (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Joan Benny wedding,., March 9, 1953. (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - CBS biographical data.. (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - NBC biographical data.. (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Biography.., 6 pages. (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Biography.., 2 pages. (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Biographical data--stories & articles.. (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Biographical data--byline stories.. (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Biography--Dennis Day.. (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Biography--Mary Livingstone.. (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Empty personalized jewelry case.. (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Louella Parsons dinner, --speech.., March 4, 1948. (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Jack Benny's birthday special--script,., February 17, 1969. (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Jack Benny Hour III--script,., March 20, 1968. (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Jack Benny's bag--script,., November 16, 1968. (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Tax info,., 1939-1953. (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Property appraisals for charity,., 1956-1958. (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Jack & Mary Benny tax file,., 1952. (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Tax files,., 1946-1951. (Box 86)
  - MCA--AFRA TV & AFTRA agreements,., 1947-1958. (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Contract--Fontainbleu Hotel, Miami.. (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Contract & ammendment, Lever Brothers,., 1959. (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - To be or not to be,., 1941-1955. (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Revue productions contracts, The face is familiar,., 1954-1957. (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - MCA--SAG agreement,., 1947-1956. (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous contracts,., 1949-1959. (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous agreements.. (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - American Tobacco Company,., 1944-1946. (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Lions, A.N.S., Incorporated.. (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Miniature Volt Corporation contract,., 1949-1950. (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Writers agreements, --television programs.., 1951-1952. (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Milton Josefberg,., 1944. (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - John Takaberry,., 1944. (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Sam Perrin,., 1944-1950. (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - George Balzer,., 1944-1946. (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Revue Jack Benny agreements,., 1950. (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Variety revue--Curran Theater, San Francisco,., 1953. (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - 1954 Summer tour.. (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - 1952 European tour.. (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Biographical data, stories & articles.. (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Awards.. (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Biography--Don Wilson.. (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Biography--cast miscellaneous.. (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper articles up to., 1947-1948. (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper articles,., 1948-1949. (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper articles,., 1949-1950. (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper articles,., 1950-1951. (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper articles,., 1951-1952. (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper articles,., 1952-1953. (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper articles,., 1953-1954. (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper articles,., 1954-1955. (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper articles,., 1955-1956. (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - National Retarded Children's week,., November 13-23, 1955-1956. (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - Biographical data--byline stories.. (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - Periodicals.. (Box 90)
  - Groucho Marx promotion, etc.,., 1949-1950. (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous,., 1947-1948. (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Personal appearance tour,., May 16-June 5, 1949-1950. (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Burns & Allen promotion,., 1949-1950. (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Cleveland, RKO Palace Theater appearance, 1 week,., June 18 1948. (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Detroit, Fox Detroit Theater appearance, 1 week,., June 10, 1948. (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Shamrock Charity Ball, Houston,., December 17, 1948. (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Tie-ups--endorsements, advertising, exploitation,., 1950-1951. (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Tie-ups--endorsements, releases, advertising, exploitation,., 1954-1955. (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Tie-ups, advertising,., 1947-1948. (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Barbara Stanwyck.. (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Andy Devine.. (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Orson Welles contracts.. (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Patsy Flick.. (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Vizvary, Alex.. (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Morris Golden [Steward Morgan Dancers].. (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Walter Winchell.. (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Benny Goodman.. (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Dick Haymes.. (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Steve Hannagan,., 1944. (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Steve Hannagan,., 1947. (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Sam Hearn.. (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Nat Hiken.. (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Irving Fein.. (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - Cy Howard.. (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - Marilyn Maxwell.. (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - Harry James.. (Box 92, Folder 17)
  - Frank Renley.. (Box 92, Folder 18)
  - Richard Lane.. (Box 92, Folder 19)
  - Abe Lyman.. (Box 92, Folder 20)
  - Butterfly McQueen.. (Box 92, Folder 21)
  - George Metaxe.. (Box 92, Folder 22)
  - Stan Myers & his orchestra.. (Box 92, Folder 23)
  - Ray Milland agreement.. (Box 92, Folder 24)
  - William Morrow.. (Box 92, Folder 25)
  - Robert Thomas O'Brien.. (Box 92, Folder 26)
  - Harry Pincus [Liazeed, Arabs].. (Box 92, Folder 27)
  - Greg Robertson.. (Box 92, Folder 28)
  - Contracts with Jeanine Roose.. (Box 92, Folder 29)
  - Photographs--Jack Benny & caricatures.. (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Photographs--Jack Benny casts, season.., 1960-1961. (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Photographs--Jack Benny casts, season.., 1964-1965. (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Photographs--Pablo Casals & Jack Benny,., 1960. (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Photographs--Cancer show, West Palm Beach,., March 20, 1966. (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Photographs--Doris Dodge & Jack Benny.. (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Photographs--Astronaut dinner, Houston,., January 30, 1966. (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Photographs--caricatures.. (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Jack Benny Productions general ledger,., 1945-1946. (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - CBS contracts,., 1948-1957. (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - CBS television casts,., 1953-1955. (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - American Tobacco Company,., 1947-1959. (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Theatrical equipment,., 1954. (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - San Francisco Curran engagement insurance--props & libel,., 1953. (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - American Tobacco Company,., 1951-1952. (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Jack Benny Revue, Curran Theater, San Francisco,., 1953. (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Jack Benny Enterprises, Incorporated,., 1946. (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Benny Colman production,., 1949. (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Jack & Mary Benny, general,., 1947-1949. (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - NBC Radio Time correspondence,., 1941-1949. (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence,., 1941-1947. (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Statuettes.., 1 broken. (Box 95)
  - Memorabilia.. (Box 96)
  - Exploitation & travel accounts,., 1945-1947. (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - American Tobacco Company,., 1947. (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - American Tobacco Company--Paul M. Hahn,., 1946. (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Statements of expenditures...., 1945. (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - American Tobacco Company,., 1945. (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - American Tobacco Company,., 1944. (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous,., 1943-1949. (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Jack Benny,., 1949-1954. (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Contracts correspondence,., 1938-1954. (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Amusement Enterprises--Lucky Stiff.. (Box 98, Folder 1-6)
  - Amusement Enterprises business papers.. (Box 98, Folder 7-14)
  - Sale of stock in Amusement Enterprises.. (Box 98, Folder 15)
  - Benny options in Amusement Enterprises.. (Box 98, Folder 16)
  - Edmund Beloin.. (Box 98, Folder 17)
  - Beloin, Morrow, Birnes [Buck Benny Rides Again].. (Box 98, Folder 18)
  - Harry M. Baldwin.. (Box 98, Folder 19)
  - Herman Birney [Howard Snyder & High Wedlock].. (Box 98, Folder 20)
  - Harry W. Conn.. (Box 98, Folder 21)
  - Periodicals.. (Box 99)
  - Statuettes and awards.. (Box 100)
  - Friars award,., 1957. (Box 101)
  - Awards and plaques.. (Box 102)
  - Statuettes and awards.. (Box 103)
  - Bowling ball and gold records.. (Box 104)
  - Awards and trophies.. (Box 105)
  - Awards, trophies, deflated autographed football.. (Box 106)
  - Plaques.. (Box 107)
  - Jack Benny's journal,; records, photographs--Harrah's Club, Lake Tahoe (Wayne Newton & Jack Benny, ).., July/August 1943 1964. (Box 108)
  - Plaques.. (Box 109)
  - Plaques and awards.. (Box 110)
  - Record (former package 1) and framed awards.. (Box 111)
  - Awards.. (Box 112-113)
  - Plaques and framed awards.. (Box 114)
  - Cups, statuettes and menorah.. (Box 115)
  - Birthday memorabilia.. (Box 116)
  - Lucky Strike Program-- Bound volume.., September 26, 1946-January 26, 1947. (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Lucky Strike Program-- Bound volume.., February 2, 1947-May 25, 1947. (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Lucky Strike Program-- Bound volume.., January 27, 1952-June 1, 1952. (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Lucky Strike Program-- Bound volume.., September 4, 1952-January 18, 1953. (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Lucky Strike Program--Bound volume.., January 25/53--6/7/53. (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Lucky Strike Program-- Bound volume.., September 13, 1953-January 24, 1954. (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Lucky Strike Program-- Bound volume.., September 26, 1954-January 23, 1955. (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Lucky Strike Program-- Bound volume.., January 30, 1955-May 22, 1955. (Box 120, Folder 2)